let savollar28 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to ache",
      answer: "C. og'rimoq",
      options: [
        "A. davolamoq",
        "B. tinchlanmoq",
        "C. og'rimoq",
        "D. rohatlanmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "arctic",
      answer: "B. arktika",
      options: [
        "A. issiq",
        "B. arktika",
        "C. o'rtacha",
        "D. subtropik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "canal",
      answer: "A. kanal",
      options: [
        "A. kanal",
        "B. daryo",
        "C. ko'l",
        "D. dengiz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "chemist",
      answer: "C. kimyogar",
      options: [
        "A. shifokor",
        "B. o'qituvchi",
        "C. kimyogar",
        "D. muhandis"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "chill",
      answer: "D. sovuq",
      options: [
        "A. istima",
        "B. harorat",
        "C. issiq",
        "D. sovuq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "congress",
      answer: "B. kongress",
      options: [
        "A. hukumat",
        "B. kongress",
        "C. sud",
        "D. vazirlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "dairy",
      answer: "A. sutli",
      options: [
        "A. sutli",
        "B. go'sht mahsulotlari",
        "C. vegetarian",
        "D. vegan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to descend",
      answer: "C. tushmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ko'tarilmoq",
        "B. chiqmoq",
        "C. tushmoq",
        "D. sakramoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "grocer",
      answer: "D. oziq-ovqat sotuvchisi",
      options: [
        "A. nonvoy",
        "B. oshpaz",
        "C. qo'y boquvchi",
        "D. oziq-ovqat sotuvchisi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to hesitate",
      answer: "A. ikkilanmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ikkilanmoq",
        "B. harakatlanmoq",
        "C. davom ettimoq",
        "D. boshlemoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "institution",
      answer: "B. tashkilot",
      options: [
        "A. biznes",
        "B. tashkilot",
        "C. guruh",
        "D. savdo"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to jog",
      answer: "C. yengil yugurmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tez yugurmoq",
        "B. sakramoq",
        "C. yengil yugurmoq",
        "D. chiqmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "merchant",
      answer: "A. savdogar",
      options: [
        "A. savdogar",
        "B. rahbar",
        "C. ishchi",
        "D. xodim"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to poke",
      answer: "D. barmoq bilan itarmoq",
      options: [
        "A. urmoq",
        "B. otmoq",
        "C. tortmoq",
        "D. barmoq bilan itarmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to postpone",
      answer: "B. keyinga qoldirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. boshlashmoq",
        "B. keyinga qoldirmoq",
        "C. yakunlamoq",
        "D. davom ettirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to splash",
      answer: "C. sochilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. quymoq",
        "B. yig'moq",
        "C. sochilmoq",
        "D. tomchilamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "stubborn",
      answer: "B. qaysar",
      options: [
        "A. dangasa",
        "B. qaysar",
        "C. moslashuvchan",
        "D. ko'ngli yumshoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "suburb",
      answer: "D. shahar chekkasi",
      options: [
        "A. hudud",
        "B. shahar markazi",
        "C. poytaxt",
        "D. shahar chekkasi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "tide",
      answer: "A. suv sathi",
      options: [
        "A. suv sathi",
        "B. to'lqin",
        "C. daryo",
        "D. ko'l"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "tragedy",
      answer: "C. fojia",
      options: [
        "A. komediya",
        "B. drama",
        "C. fojia",
        "D. hikoya"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar28;